[angry] "Marcellus Wallace look"
[angry] "...like what?"
[angry] "You from what country one, hah?"
[angry] "That one no country I..."
...ever heard of lor. They speak...
...English in where? What kind of English?
Motherfucker! You speak it anot?
Yes! Then you know what...
...I talking, right? Yes! Describe what...
...Marcellus Wallace look like.
What sia?! Say what again! Say...
...what again! I dare you!
I double dare you lah! Say...
...what one more f***ing time, siao ah!
He black colour. Go on. He...
...botak. He look like...
...a bitch, hah? What?!
He look like a...
...bitch anot? No! Then why you...
...go and try to f*** him like...
...a bitch, Brett? I never do!
Ya lah, you did! Ya, you...
...did, Brett! You go and try to...
...f*** him! No! Marcellus Wallace...
...don't like people f*** him...
...by anybody 'cept Mrs. Wallace lah!
You read Bible anot, Brett?
Ya! Oh, got this passage...
...I already memorized. Kinda...
...damn fit this occasion. Ezekiel 25...
...17.
The path of the righteous man...
...is all around kena by...
...the bad things of...
...the selfish and the cruel ways...
...of evil men.
Blessed is the one who, in...
...the name of charity and good...
...will, go shepherd the weak through...
...the valley of darkness, because...
...he is truly his brother's...
...keeper and the one who find...
...lost children. Then I will...
...come strike down on you with...
...very big revenge and super angry...
...for those who try to poison...
...and destroy my brothers. Then...
...you will know my name...
...is the Lord when I...
...give my revenge to you.